And the complete meaning is that how much do we incur in the
100% insurance claim that you people give,
and
if we talk about the rest, for example,
about the insurance claim of a bike, suppose if
we want to make an insurance claim for Bajaj Pulsar 125, then what is
its
process, what
documents are required in it, insurance
registration, driving license, PAN card,
Aadhar card, okay, so what will be the process in that,
how will we have to make the claim,
like if our bike met with an accident today, then
you bring the bike and how did the accident happen,
accidental license, who was driving the car,
after that we will make the claim, after that there will be a
survey in 244 to 48 hours, next day if the
parts are available then you will
get the car within three days, okay, so if the parts are
available then it means the
bike will be given to us within three days,
okay, and the complete meaning is that how much do we incur in the
100% insurance claim that you people give, that is,
if you see the total, the company will deduct and
give you D in it  My DO will come,
whatever the bill will be, suppose the bill is of 10000, the company
gave me a DO of 9900, then you have to pay ₹1
and what does it mean, the charge for making a claim, there is
no charge, it is
automatically detected, well, it means there is no separate
charge, there is no separate charge,
that DO and whatever difference comes in that amount,
you have to pay that only, like what happens to many people, like there is
some charge for making an insurance claim, 200 or
300, that company deducts,
when your DO comes, the claim charge is deducted in it,
well, automatically, like you gave a car, you had an
accident, we repaired the car, your
bill was of 00, the company has to give us 9000 or
000, so it means if
we take 100% claim, which is called zero dep
insurance, then the base company
salvage in it, like suppose your
tank got damaged, salvage will be deducted from 5 to 10, that
means approximately 10  Still, it gets deducted, that is
rare, like suppose a big item
goes in the fuel tank, it goes in the silencer, the
rim alloy will all be changed, it goes in that, it will
not go like this, so we get 100% claim, that is,
in which parts,
how much of the fiber item do we have, that is
100%,
that is why we get 100% and the company
deducts salvage, it does not happen with our ad,
and whichever company's policy you deduct, that
salvage will be
deducted, like you suppose ma'am, what are we doing,
ma'am will deduct the salvage and give you the
payment for the delivery order,
show that to the customer, take your money, then the
extra difference that is coming will have to be
paid by the customer, and if the customer is adding
something on his own, then that has to be given to them in the payment,
which is not getting passed, if your less
charges remain, that is, like the
charges for fitting etc., the company pays the
entire company total and like many people
also ask that in it, like liquid  Are the
items etc. covered or
not? Are the items under 00 also covered or
not? For example, if I have
some problem in the engine of my bike
or I take an insurance claim, then in that,
like the engine oil etc. which is
filled in it, will it be available or will it have to be filled,
engine, battery, tyres, all this is not covered, okay, that is not covered,
okay, otherwise if we
talk about warranty, then if we
want to take a claim,
what all is covered in the warranty, warranty is your
engine warranty for one year, all the items like ACU
in the car, if it gets damaged
then you also get it under warranty, there
is a regulator, many things are covered under warranty, I mean,
you should explain to us in detail
what all is covered under warranty, why is there a full engine warranty for
one year, okay, your clutch plate is
not covered under warranty, okay, for example, suppose there is a
scratch in your tank,
I mean, there is some fault in the paint, that is
also covered under warranty, but there should not be a physical dent,
okay, I mean, do not cause dents yourself, I
mean, only due to fading etc.
If it has happened then we get warranty for it,
sometimes the headlight turns yellow, that too is covered under
warranty if it should not be damaged, it
is fine and then if it shorts,
it is an all in one sensor, pump and sensor etc.
like now the T sensor is coming and
warranty of other things is also covered by one year, in that too by one year but
your service history should be correct,
many people get the first, second or
third service done and then they go to the market, if they go to the market then there is no
service after that, our history will not be
visible, then how will you give warranty to him, so the
service history should be visible for them, I
mean the service history, that is, how should it be, it should be
in the company, whether it is
done at our place or any authorized dealer, if the service is done
at an authorized dealer then there will be no problem in the warranty,
then there will be no problem and the
paid service will also be provided by us, that is, authorized
dealer or dealer and if we get it done outside then if we take
warranty, then see the warranty is available,
he can give it to his dealer, if he does not
want to give it, that is, at the dealer's end, then it is whether
he will give it or not, if
you get the service done then no dealer will
give it, that is, if we get the service done at another dealer
Yes and if we want to make a warranty claim here then
we will provide the service, the
warranty will be given, the service should be theirs, if it is
authorized in the market in the updated CDM thera then it will
not be there, so if by mistake
one or two services are missed then there is
some problem in that, does the company
ask you to do three services in a year, we have to do a
gap of 10000 first pass, it is not like that, do
10000 passes after 2000 kilometers,
then 15, then 20, then 25, so the company is also giving
you a gap now suppose if there
is a customer, suppose if he gets a
service done somewhere else by mistake, after that
if there is some warranty in his bike, then the last two
services are checked, if you
give warranty for anything then it is
checked whether the last two services were done in the showroom or not,
well if that remains then you will get it, yes you will get it, so
friends this was the complete
process on this, in which we
told you the complete process of insurance claim and
we also explained the entire process of the rest of the warranty here,
we would
like to say special thanks here Sagar  Bhaiya
who has helped us a lot here,
if you have any doubts then you
can ask us by commenting, this was all in today's
video friends, I will
meet you soon in the next video, till then
I am Satyam Gupta, signing off, thank
you friends.